This is the another file which is created using the terminal window
The lead developer is focusing on the new changes to be developed.
Now, as we know we've 3 team members so we should be focusing on getting things done using our team work.
/* Team lead has gotten a task to fix the bug without knowing that the developer 2 has already thought of fixing the same bug.
However, team lead will fix the bug and commit his changes.
